https://www.mercyhs.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy - Our Lady of Mercy
Skip to contentClick to read about Mercy’s HyFlex Learning Model and Back-to-School plans.
AcademicsBack-to-School Plan 2020All-Girl DifferenceMiddle SchoolHigh SchoolCollege PlanningInternationalOur FacultyAdmissionsVirtual Open House 2020Your JourneyApply for AdmissionTuition and Financial AidPlan a VisitFAQsCampus LifeStudent WellnessSpiritualityTraditionsClubsMercy ServicePerforming ArtsAthleticsSection V and Club SportsAthletic ScheduleSports BoostersAboutLife ChangingHistoryMission and ValuesSchool ProfileLeadershipLife of a Mercy GirlNews and Student SuccessPublicationsPhoto GalleriesEmployment19th AmendmentGiveSuzanne Johnston ScholarshipCOVID-19 FundWhy it MattersWays to GiveMercy FundAlumnae GivingPlanned GivingEventsPlan a VisitAlumnaeCareer ConnectionsLegacy FamiliesAlumnae EventsAwardsGet InvolvedAlumnae GivingTranscriptsStudent-Parent PortalBookstore
BookstoreAlumnaeStudent-Parent Portal Search
MENUMENUAcademicsBack-to-School Plan 2020All-Girl DifferenceMiddle SchoolHigh SchoolCollege PlanningInternationalOur FacultyAdmissionsVirtual Open House 2020Your JourneyApply for AdmissionTuition and Financial AidPlan a VisitFAQsCampus LifeStudent WellnessSpiritualityTraditionsClubsMercy ServicePerforming ArtsAthleticsSection V and Club SportsAthletic ScheduleSports BoostersAboutLife ChangingHistoryMission and ValuesSchool ProfileLeadershipLife of a Mercy GirlNews and Student SuccessPublicationsPhoto GalleriesEmployment19th AmendmentGiveSuzanne Johnston ScholarshipCOVID-19 FundWhy it MattersWays to GiveMercy FundPlanned GivingEventsApply NowPrivacy PolicyThank you for visiting the Our Lady of Mercy School for Young Women web site. Please take a moment and review our Privacy Statement. Mercy is committed to respecting the privacy and security of all users of our web site, and to ensuring that we protect the rights of the Mercy community. Our policy describes the types of information that are included on our web site and how it may be used. Mercy’s Privacy Statement may require updates occasionally. We encourage you to review this Privacy Statement each time you visit our web site.PERSONAL INFORMATIONMercy does not collect personal information from users of our web site without their knowledge. Personal information may be requested from you when you participate in certain online activities, including:Using or sending e-mail to a Mercy provided e-mail account.Completing and submitting a form to Mercy via an online application, comment form, survey form, or similar online form available on our web site.Personal information you provide is used for the purpose for which it is collected and may be shared with employees, agents, and contractors of Mercy for the purpose for which it was submitted.ANONYMOUS INFORMATION – LOG FILESThe Mercy web site automatically records a limited amount of demographic information from the users of the school’s web site, which may include the country of origin of the visit, operating system and browser type that is used, frequency of visits, and other similar information. This information is collected and used for statistical analysis and comparison purposes only. Mercy uses the information collected and the related analysis to help us communicate with its constituents more effectively.COOKIES AND LINKSA “cookie” is a piece of data stored on the user’s hard drive containing information about the user. It enables Mercy to store and track what a user of the Mercy web site is looking at during a visit. If you are concerned about the potential use of information gathered from your computer by cookies, you can set your browser to prompt you before it accepts a cookie. Most internet browsers have settings that allow the identification or rejection of cookies. If you decide not to permit the use of cookies during your visit to Mercy’s web site, you may be unable to use certain functions on our web site.The Mercy web site provides links to other web sites. Mercy is not responsible for the privacy statements or content of other web sites. Mercy’s Privacy Statement does not apply when visiting non-Mercy sites.SECURITYMercy takes precautions to protect the personal information gathered through our web site. When personal information is submitted, it is stored in a secure file on a Mercy server maintained in a secure environment and its access is restricted to authorized employees of Mercy. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific task are granted access to personal information.GLOBAL SECURITY BREACHThis Privacy Statement describes, generally, how information is collected by the Mercy web site and how the information collected is used by Mercy. This is Privacy Statement does not constitute a guarantee of privacy, as it is possible for information collected to be disclosed without Mercy’s knowledge or permission in certain circumstances. Although it is rare, in spite of extensive security measures, there is always a risk of an attack on the Internet host or a compromise of security as a result of a virus. Mercy may also disclose certain information if it is required to do so by law or if we believe, in good faith, that such disclosure is necessary to (a) protect the rights and interests of Mercy or (b) protect the safety of any individual or the general public.QUESTIONS OR COMMENTS?If you have questions about this privacy statement or comments about the web site, e-mail Dave Carro, Director of Marketing and Communications at qpneeb@zrepluf.pbz or write to us at:Webmaster Our Lady of Mercy High School 1437 Blossom Road Rochester, NY 14610Experience the Circle of MercyTo truly understand how life changing Mercy is, schedule a visit. Tour the campus, meet us in person, and talk to our students and staff. From information sessions and tours, there are many ways to learn about the Circle of Mercy. Your Journey to Mercy
1437 Blossom Road Rochester, NY 14610 Phone: 585-288-7120Fax:
585-288-7966
vasb@zrepluf.pbz Mercy is a ministry of the Sisters of MercyAcademicsBack-to-School Plan 2020All-Girl DifferenceMiddle SchoolHigh SchoolCollege PlanningInternationalOur FacultyAdmissionsVirtual Open House 2020Your JourneyApply for AdmissionTuition and Financial AidPlan a VisitFAQsCampus LifeStudent WellnessSpiritualityTraditionsClubsMercy ServicePerforming ArtsAthleticsSection V and Club SportsAthletic ScheduleSports BoostersAboutLife ChangingHistoryMission and ValuesSchool ProfileLeadershipLife of a Mercy GirlNews and Student SuccessPublicationsPhoto GalleriesEmployment19th AmendmentGiveSuzanne Johnston ScholarshipCOVID-19 FundWhy it MattersWays to GiveMercy FundAlumnae GivingPlanned GivingEventsPlan a VisitAlumnaeCareer ConnectionsLegacy FamiliesAlumnae EventsAwardsGet InvolvedAlumnae GivingTranscriptsStudent-Parent PortalBookstore© 2020 Our Lady of Mercy School for Young Women.Privacy PolicyWeb AccessibilitySafety and SecurityDesigned by Mason Digital. Keep in Touch with us!Have you moved, changed schools, changed jobs? Have you added to your family? Would you like to come and visit? We love hearing from our alumnae! Name*
First
Last Maiden NameClass Year*Mailing Address
Street Address
Address Line 2
City
State / Province / Region
ZIP / Postal Code
AfghanistanAlbaniaAlgeriaAmerican SamoaAndorraAngolaAnguillaAntarcticaAntigua and BarbudaArgentinaArmeniaArubaAustraliaAustriaAzerbaijanBahamasBahrainBangladeshBarbadosBelarusBelgiumBelizeBeninBermudaBhutanBoliviaBonaire, Sint Eustatius and SabaBosnia and HerzegovinaBotswanaBouvet IslandBrazilBritish Indian Ocean TerritoryBrunei DarussalamBulgariaBurkina FasoBurundiCambodiaCameroonCanadaCape VerdeCayman IslandsCentral African RepublicChadChileChinaChristmas IslandCocos IslandsColombiaComorosCongo, Democratic Republic of theCongo, Republic of theCook IslandsCosta RicaCroatiaCubaCuraçaoCyprusCzech RepublicCôte d'IvoireDenmarkDjiboutiDominicaDominican RepublicEcuadorEgyptEl SalvadorEquatorial GuineaEritreaEstoniaEswatini (Swaziland)EthiopiaFalkland IslandsFaroe IslandsFijiFinlandFranceFrench GuianaFrench PolynesiaFrench Southern TerritoriesGabonGambiaGeorgiaGermanyGhanaGibraltarGreeceGreenlandGrenadaGuadeloupeGuamGuatemalaGuernseyGuineaGuinea-BissauGuyanaHaitiHeard and McDonald IslandsHoly SeeHondurasHong KongHungaryIcelandIndiaIndonesiaIranIraqIrelandIsle of ManIsraelItalyJamaicaJapanJerseyJordanKazakhstanKenyaKiribatiKuwaitKyrgyzstanLao People's Democratic RepublicLatviaLebanonLesothoLiberiaLibyaLiechtensteinLithuaniaLuxembourgMacauMacedoniaMadagascarMalawiMalaysiaMaldivesMaliMaltaMarshall IslandsMartiniqueMauritaniaMauritiusMayotteMexicoMicronesiaMoldovaMonacoMongoliaMontenegroMontserratMoroccoMozambiqueMyanmarNamibiaNauruNepalNetherlandsNew CaledoniaNew ZealandNicaraguaNigerNigeriaNiueNorfolk IslandNorth KoreaNorthern Mariana IslandsNorwayOmanPakistanPalauPalestine, State ofPanamaPapua New GuineaParaguayPeruPhilippinesPitcairnPolandPortugalPuerto RicoQatarRomaniaRussiaRwandaRéunionSaint BarthélemySaint HelenaSaint Kitts and NevisSaint LuciaSaint MartinSaint Pierre and MiquelonSaint Vincent and the GrenadinesSamoaSan MarinoSao Tome and PrincipeSaudi ArabiaSenegalSerbiaSeychellesSierra LeoneSingaporeSint MaartenSlovakiaSloveniaSolomon IslandsSomaliaSouth AfricaSouth GeorgiaSouth KoreaSouth SudanSpainSri LankaSudanSurinameSvalbard and Jan Mayen IslandsSwedenSwitzerlandSyriaTaiwanTajikistanTanzaniaThailandTimor-LesteTogoTokelauTongaTrinidad and TobagoTunisiaTurkeyTurkmenistanTurks and Caicos IslandsTuvaluUS Minor Outlying IslandsUgandaUkraineUnited Arab EmiratesUnited KingdomUnited StatesUruguayUzbekistanVanuatuVenezuelaVietnamVirgin Islands, BritishVirgin Islands, U.S.Wallis and FutunaWestern SaharaYemenZambiaZimbabweÅland Islands Country Email* PhoneWhat Is new with you?Have you moved, changed schools, changed jobs? Have you added to your family? Would you like to come and visit? We love hearing from our alumnae!To prove you are not a robot, please enter the answer to this math problem.NameThis field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.
Close
